Guide to the Herman W. Liebert Manuscript Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Liebert Autograph Collection, Series I
  - "M"
    - Moore, George, 1852-1933
      - ALS to the printer, 121 Ebcey Street (Jan 19, 1921) and proof of p. 5 of Memoirs of My Dead Life with author's manuscript approval for the press (Jan 31, 1921) (Box 3, Folder 94-95)
    - More, Hannah, 1745-1833
      - Autograph manuscript verses, signed, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 96)
        Six four-line stanzas.
    - Mosby, John Singleton, 1833-1916
      - TLS to Mr. H. C. Jordan, Washington, D. C., 1909 Aug 23 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Mudford, William, 1782-1848
      - ALS to James Perry, Esq., No. 13 Edwin St. Jones, 1816 Sep 29 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Murray, John
      - AMS, endorsement on a receipt, Queens Arms, 1781 Aug 14 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Muybridge, Eadweard, 1830-1904
      - ALS to A. E. Jessup, Esq., 38 Craven St., Charing Cross, London, [18]89 Nov 17 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - "N"
    - Newton, John
      - ALS to Mrs. Onslow, Weston Underwood near Olney, Jul 18 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Nightingale, Florence, 1820-1910
      - ALS to Octavia Hill, [London], 1878 Mar 1
        Asks advice on behalf of Miss Kate Perssè, head of the District Nurses in Liverpool.
    - Norton, Caroline Sheridan, 1808-1877
      - 4 ALS to Mrs. William F. Cowper, London
      - ALS to [Mrs. Finlay], n.d.
      - ALS to "the Editor of the Northern Whig", n.d.
      - 4 ALS to Frank Stone, 1840, 1844, n.d.
      - ALS to Henry Taylor, [1845]
    - Noyes, Alfred, 1880-1958
      - ALS to Mr. Sutcliffe, 85 Cadogan Gardens, S. W., [19]23 May 30 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Ouida, 1839-1908
      - 11 ALS to Alfred Austin, [ca. 1890-95] (Box 3, Folder 103)
        With two envelopes.
      - ALS to unidentified correspondent, [1897] Jan 10 (Box 3, Folder 104)
      - ALS to Mr. Courtenay, [1897] Jun 25 (Box 3, Folder 105)
      - ALS to unidentified correspondent, Nov 16 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - "P"
    - Palgrave, Francis Turner, 1824-1897
      - ALS to Rossetti, Supset Hall, Wakefield, [18]67 Nov 11 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Paoli, Pasquale, 1725-1807
      - LS, Corte, 1756 Mar 6 (Box 3, Folder 108)
      - ALS to Riumo Amico, Tomino, 1761 Aug 23 (Box 3, Folder 109)
      - AL to Amico, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Pearce, Zachary, 1690-1774
      - ALS to George Rosse, 1750-51 Feb 20 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Peel, Robert, Sir, 1788-1850
      - ALS to Mr. Smith, Lulworth Castle, 1822 Oct 7 (Box 3, Folder 112)
      - ALS to unidentified correspondent, Whitechurch, Apr 27 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Pennant, Thomas, 1726-1798
      - ALS to unidentified correspondent, Downing, 1779 Jan 15 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Pennington, Montagu, 1762-1849
      - ALS to J. W. Croker, Deal, 1836 Jan 25 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Percy, Thomas, 1729-1811
      - MS, receipt to James Dodsley, 1761 Jun 10 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Phillpotts, Eden, 1862-1960
      - ALS to Coulson Kernahan, 29 Garden Rd., Ealing, 1895 Feb 8 (Box 3, Folder 117)
      - ALS to Richard Watson Gilder, Torquay, England, 1906 Oct 13 (Box 3, Folder 118)
      - AMS, poem, 1916 Nov 9 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Piozzi, Hester Lynch, 1741-1821
      - Autograph copy of letter to Miss Salusbury (Hester Lynch Piozzi) from James Marriott, 1763 Jun 30 (Box 3, Folder 120)
      - AL to unidentified correspondent, 1815 Nov 5 (Box 3, Folder 121)
      - AN in third person to Mr. Stockdale, George Street, Manchester Square, No. 5, Jul 11 (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Pissarro, Camille, 1830-1903
      - ALS to Mon Cher Docteur, Szagny, Barincourt, 1901 Jul 9 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Pitman, Issac, Sir, 1813-1897
      - AL in shorthand, [1889] (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Pitt, William, 1759-1806
      - Notes for a speech in Parliament, 1804 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Pius IX, Pope, 1792-1878
      - Two manuscript blessings, 1868 (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - Pope, Alexander, 1688-1744
      - ALS to Jonathan Richardson, 1737 Apr 20 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Porter, Jane, 1776-1850
      - ALS to Mrs. Kirby, London, 1842 Aug 8
        On the death of her brother, Robert Ker Porter.
    - Potter, Robert
      - ALS to unidentified recipient, Searning, 1787 Aug 24 (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Pye, Henry James, 1745-1813
      - ALS to Messrs. Lackington & Allen, Queen Sq. Westr., 1804 May 4 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - "R"
    - Richardson, Samuel, 1689-1761
      - ALS to [Mrs. Watts], London, 1756 May 13
    - Romney, George, 1734-1802
      - ALS to his son, the Rev. John Romney, London (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - Ros, Amanda McKittrick, 1860-1939
      - ALS to Capt. Graves, Iddesleigh, Larue Harbour, Ireland, Dec 8 (Box 3, Folder 131)
      - Autograph manuscript pages of Helen Huddleson not used in final version, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 132)
    - Rose, T. H.
      - ALS to Tom, incorporating a letter to Edward Jesse, 1831 Apr 8 (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - Rousseau, Jean-Jacques, 1712-1778
      - AN, to one of his publishers [?], n.d. (Box 3, Folder 134)
        In French. Concerning corrections in either La Nouvelle Heloise or Emile. Faint signature at foot is not Rousseau's.
  - "S"
    - Sacher-Masoch, Leopold, Ritter von, 1835-1895
      - ALS to a friend, Gwurtz [?], 1866 Jun 27 (Box 3, Folder 135)
        In German.
    - Schurz, Carl, 1829-1906
      - ALS to Falka, Hamburg, 1862 Jan 9 (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Silliman, Benjamin, 1779-1864
      - ALS to Prof. Cleaveland, New Haven, 1823 Jan 27 (Box 3, Folder 137)
      - ALS to Prof. Alexander, New Haven, [18]64 Jul 10 (Box 3, Folder 138)
    - Smith, Horace, 1779-1849
      - Untitled manuscript poem, signed, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - Smith, James, 1775-1839
      - Epigram to Miss Edgeworth, signed J. S., 1822 Jun 19 (Box 3, Folder 140)
      - ALS to [Thomas] Hill, [London], 1809 Jun 13
      - AN in the third person to Mrs. Smith, [London], May 4
    - Smith, Madeleine Hamilton, 1835-1928
      - 3 ALS to Emile, Lodgings Hill, B. M. L., n.d. (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - Somerville, E. OE. (Edith Oenone), 1858-1949
      - 8 ALS and postcards to Sylvia Warren, Tally Ho House, Castletownshend, County Cork, 1947, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - Spencer, Hergert, 1820-1903
      - Autograph additions and corrections of two pages from first edition of Principles of Psychology (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - Sterling, George, 1869-1926
      - ALS to Donald Clifford Gallup, n.d.
        On same page as ALS from Gallup to Sterling, 1907 Aug 31, Overlook, Coxsackie-on-Hudson, New York, requesting Sterling's autograph.
    - Stockdale, Percival, 1736-1811
      - Manuscript transcript of a letter to Dr. Samuel Johnson, Hinxworth, near Balock, Hertfordshere, 1780 Oct 31 (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - Strahan, George, 1744-1824
      - Autograph receipt signed to Thomas Cadell, 1787 Jan 31 (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - Swinburne, J. E.
      - ALS to Sir W. Wood, Caphenton, N. Cenlle, 1851 Jan 21 (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - "T"
    - Taylor, John
      - ALS to J. W. Croker, 92 Norton Street, Portland Place, 1829 Mar 2 (Box 3, Folder 147)
      - ALS to J. W. Croker, 92 Norton Street, Portland Place, 1829 Aug 4 (Box 3, Folder 148)
      - ALS to J. W. Croker, 92 Norton Street, Portland Place, 1829 Aug 5 (Box 3, Folder 149)
      - ALS to unidentified correspondent, 92 Norton Street, Portland Place, 1829 Sep 30 (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - Temple, Jane Barnard
      - AL in third person to Dr. Johnson, [ca. 1781] (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - Tennyson, Alfred Tennyson, Baron, 1809-1892
      - ALS to Mr. Tupper, Harringford, Freshwater, Isle of Wight, 1868 Jun 30 (Box 3, Folder 152)
    - Tennyson Association
      - List of dilapidations accrued at No. 7 Upper Winpole Street during the tenancy of A. Tennyson, Esq., 1877 May 16 (Box 3, Folder 153)
    - Thornton, Bonnell, 1724-1768
      - ALS to Henry Sampson Woodfall, n.d.
    - Tomlinson, H. M. (Henry Major), 1873-1958
      - "The Estuary", n.d.
        Typescript, with autograph manuscript corrections.
    - Tupper, Martin Farquhar, 1810-1889
      - 5 ALS to various correspondents, 1843-46 (Box 3, Folder 154)
      - 4 ALS to various correspondents, 1847-48 (Box 3, Folder 155)
      - 5 ALS to various correspondents, 1849 (Box 3, Folder 156)
      - 5 ALS to various correspondents, 1850 (Box 3, Folder 157)
      - 4 ALS to various correspondents, 1851-52 (Box 3, Folder 158)
      - 5 ALS to various correspondents, 1853-54 (Box 3, Folder 159)
      - 4 ALS to various correspondents, 1857-59 (Box 3, Folder 160)
      - 4 ALS to various correspondents, 1860-63 (Box 3, Folder 161)
      - 5 ALS to various correspondents, 1864-65 (Box 3, Folder 162)
      - 3 ALS to various correspondents, 1866 (Box 3, Folder 163)
      - 6 ALS to various correspondents, 1867 (Box 3, Folder 164)
      - 3 ALS to various correspondents, 1868 (Box 3, Folder 165)
      - 6 ALS to various correspondents, 1870-77 (Box 4, Folder 166)
      - 5 ALS to various correspondents, 1880, 1882 (Box 4, Folder 167)
      - ALS to "Master Jordan," Hastings, 1882 Nov 4
        Contains a signed verse beginning "How many years have fled."
      - 4 ALS to various correspondents, 1883-85 (Box 4, Folder 168)
      - 8 ALS to various correspondents (Box 4, Folder 169)
        2 incomplete.
      - Signed, printed broadside, "What England Hopes", 1871 Dec (Box 4, Folder 170)
      - 6 autograph manuscripts, 1853-58, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 171)
      - 2 photographs, 2 engravings, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 172)
      - Recollections of My Schooldays, autograph manuscript, signed, Norwood, 1884 (Box 4, Folder 173)
      - Recollections of My Schooldays, autograph manuscript, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 174)
  - "V"
    - Vanbrugh, John, Sir, 1664-1726
      - 2 manuscript bills for work done on Blenheim Castle, 1709 May (Box 4, Folder 175)
    - Vlaminck, Maurice de, 1876-1958
      - ALS to unidentified correspondent, La Tourillière, Rueil-la-Gadelière (Box 4, Folder 176)
  - "W"
    - Walmesly, Gilbert, 1680-1751
      - Autograph signature attached to a manuscript fragment, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 177)
    - Warton, Thomas, 1728-1790
      - Receipt, signed, to the Lord Chamberlain, 1787 Apr 5 (Box 4, Folder 178)
    - Watts-Dunton, Theodore, 1832-1914
      - LS to Mr. Salaman, The Pines, 11 Putney Hill, S. W., 1907 Apr 3 (Box 4, Folder 179)
      - ALS to an unidentified recipient, Putney Hill, [London], 1882 Apr 16
        Refers to the death of Dante Gabriel Rossetti.
    - Waugh, Evelyn, 1903-1966
      - ALS to Murphy, Hyde Park Hotel, Knightsbridge, London, S. W. 1 (Box 4, Folder 180)
    - Wells, Carolyn, d. 1942
      - ALS to Edw[ard] F. Allen, Rahway, N.J., 1914 Nov 7
    - Whitefoord, Caleb, 1734-1810
      - ALS to Charles Townley, London, 1794 May 5 (Box 4, Folder 181)
    - Wilkie, David, Sir, 1785-1841
      - ALS to C. L. Eastlake, Kensington, 1816 Oct 25 (Box 4, Folder 182)
    - Wise, Thomas
      - ALS to R. W. Chapman, Kirkstead, 25 Heath Drive, Hampstead, N. W. 3, [18]23 Mar 21 (Box 4, Folder 183)
    - Wolfe, Humbert, 1885-1940
      - Translation of Edmond Rostand's "Cyrano de Bergerac"
        Typewritten manuscript. Accompanied by a typewritten manuscript of the preface by Wolfe.
    - Wordsworth, William, 1770-1850
      - ALS to Dr. John Davy, Rydal Mt., [1839] Aug 21 (Box 4, Folder 184)
  - "Z"
    - Zamenhof, L. L. (Ludwik Lazar), 1859-1917
      - ALS to unidentified correspondent, Varsovio, str. Dzika No. 9 (Box 4, Folder 185)
  - UNIDENTIFIED
    - Possibly a legal document regarding Michael Johnson's freedom of Litchfield, 1710 Dec (Box 4, Folder 186)
    - ALS from Daniel O'Connor, Assistant Assessor, to Peter Orr, Marysville, 1864 Sep 26 (Box 4, Folder 187)
      Concerns penalties assessed for failure of Orr to pay his taxes.
    - ALS from Derick S. Thomson to Mr. Duval, University of Glasgow, 1987 Jul 6 (Box 4, Folder 188)
      Concerning Comh-chruinneachidh Orannaigh Gaidhealach. With 2 related notes.
    - Fragments of text removed from John Seager, A supplement to Dr. Johnson's Dictionary of the English Language... (London: Printed by A. J. Valpy..., 1819) (Box 4, Folder 189)
    - Manuscript notes removed from Mary Ann Hanway, A Journey to the Highlands of Scotland... (London: Printed for Fielding and Walker, [1776?] (Box 4, Folder 190)
- Liebert Correspondence, Series II
  - "A"
    - Amory, Cleveland
      - 1 ALS and 2 TLS to HWL, 1948
  - "F"
    - Fleming, Ian, 1908-1964
      - 7 TLS to HWL, 4 Old Mitre Court, Fleet Street, E. C. 4, Ludgate Circus, 1961-64 (Box 4, Folder 191)
  - "L"
    - Lunt, Alfred
      - ALS to HWL, 150 East End Avenue, New York (N.Y.), [1969 Feb 17]
  - "M"
    - Maugham, W. Somerset (William Somerset), 1874-1965
      - TLS to HWL, 1961 Sep 26
    - Mencken, H. L. (Henry Louis), 1880-1956
      - 4 TLS to HWL, 1524 Hollins St., Baltimore, 1948
  - "N"
    - Nabokov, Vladimir Vladimirovich, 1899-1977
      - TLS to HWL, Montreux-Palace Hotel, Montreux, Switzerland, 1969 May 30
    - Nathan, George Jean, 1882-1958
      - ALS to HWL, 44 West 44th Street, New York, 1948 Jan 12
    - Nichols, Beverly
      - ALS to HWL, The Waldorf-Astoria, New York, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 192)
  - "O"
    - O'Hara, John, 1905-1970
      - 4 TLS to HWL, 55 East 86th Street, New York, 1948
    - Osborn, Robert Chesley, 1904-
      - ALS to HWL, Salisbury, Conn., [19]68 Sep 14
  - "P"
    - Powys, John Cowper, 1872-1963
      - AL to HWL, 1 Waterloo, Blaenau-festiniog, Merionethshire, North Wales, 1958 Dec 28 (Box 4, Folder 193)
  - "V"
    - Van Doren, Mark, 1894-1972
      - ALS to HWL, Falls Village, Conn., 1969 Oct 19
  - "W"
    - Wilder, Isabel, 1900-
      - 3 ALS and 1 TLS to HWL, 1977-79
        With envelopes.
    - Wilder, Thornton, 1897-1975
      - Autograph card to HWL, 50 Deepwood Drive, Hamden 14, Conn., 1948 [Feb 22] (Box 4, Folder 194)
      - ALS to HWL, c/o Americ[an] Exp[ress] Co., 11 rue Scribe, Paris, [1957 Apr 15]
      - Pencil drawing, Farmington, Conn., 1962 Apr 5 (Box 4, Folder 195)
        Made during reading of Ch. 12 of W. S. Lewis's One Man's Education.
      - ALS to HWL, 50 Deepwood Drive, Hamden, Conn., 1967 Apr 12 (Box 4, Folder 196)
      - 4 ALS to HWL, 1967-75
      - ALS to Lola [Liebert], n.d. (Box 4, Folder 197)
- Additions Since 1996, 1781 Mar 9; Series III
  - Burke, Edmund to John Noble, 1781 Mar 9 (Box 5, Folder 198)
  - Bute, John Stuart, 1st Marquess of, to Sir William Hamilton, 1764-81 (Box 5, Folder 199)
  - Carter, Frederick. "The Old Actor", 1940 Oct 10
  - Cunninghame Graham, R. B. (Robert Bontine) to Walter Crane, 1887 Dec 1 (Box 5, Folder 200)
  - Day, Nicholas. Portrait of Arthur Machen, 1934 Mar 31
  - Dowden, Edward
    - to Robert Browning, 1866 Feb 15 (Box 5, Folder 201)
    - to Professor Rudmose-Brown, 1910 Apr 20 (Box 5, Folder 202)
  - Garrick, David
    - "Epilogue" written for Arthur Murphy's Know Your Own Mind, [1777] (Box 5, Folder 203)
    - [Little Busy, Bustling Will], 1777 (Box 5, Folder 204)
  - Gilbert, W. S. (William Schwenck) to [Burnand?], 1891 Oct 19 (Box 5, Folder 205)
  - Gosse, Edmund
    - to John Kendrick Bangs, 1887 Oct 13 (Box 5, Folder 206)
    - to John H. Ingram, 1877 Jan 1 (Box 5, Folder 207)
    - to Frank Lester Pleadwell, 1926, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 208)
    - to Grant Richards, 1902 Mar 19 (Box 5, Folder 209)
    - to Sir Humphrey Rolleston, 1923-26 (Box 5, Folder 210)
    - to Mr. [G. M.?] Williamson, 1902 May 13 (Box 5, Folder 211)
    - "The Pipe Player", n.d. (Box 5, Folder 212)
  - Gosse, Ellen, Lady, to John Lane, 1894 Apr 13 (Box 5, Folder 213)
  - Haggard, H. Rider (Henry Rider) to William Loeb, 1905 Mar 10 (Box 5, Folder 214)
  - Hardy, Thomas to Jerome K. Jerome, 1894 Aug 26 (Box 5, Folder 215)
  - Hawker, Peter to Robert Rising, 1841 Nov 7 (Box 5, Folder 216)
  - Haydon, Benjamin Robert to Alaric Watts, 1827 Mar 15 (Box 5, Folder 217)
  - Hogg, James
    - to Dr. J[ohn Clarke-] Whitfield, 1816 Jan 18 (Box 5, Folder 218)
    - to an unidentified recipient, 1824 Jul 11 (Box 5, Folder 219)
  - Hunt, Leigh. Miscellaneous collection of autograph manuscripts, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 220)
  - Jerrold, Douglas William to Dudley Costello, 1848 May 6 (Box 5, Folder 221)
  - Maugham, W. Somerset (William Somerset) to [Herman W.] Liebert, 1961 Sep 26 (Box 5, Folder 222)
  - Mitford, Mary Russell to an unidentified recipient, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 223)
  - Nightingale, Florence to Octavia Hill, 1878 Mar 1 (Box 5, Folder 224)
  - Norton, Caroline Sheridan
    - to Mrs. William F. Cowper, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 225)
    - to [Mrs. Finlay], n.d. (Box 5, Folder 226)
    - to "the Editor of the Northern Whig", n.d. (Box 5, Folder 227)
    - to Frank Stone, 1840, 1844, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 228)
    - to Henry Taylor, [1845] (Box 5, Folder 229)
  - Porter, Jane to Mrs. Kirby, 1842 Aug 8 (Box 5, Folder 230)
  - Richardson, Samuel to [Mrs. Watts], 1756 May 13 (Box 5, Folder 231)
  - Smith, James, 1775-1839
    - to [Thomas] Hill, 1809 Jun 13 (Box 5, Folder 232)
    - to Mrs. Smith, May 4 (Box 5, Folder 233)
  - Thornton, Bonnell to Henry Sampson Woodfall, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 234)
  - Tomlinson, H. M. (Henry Major). "The Estuary", n.d. (Box 5, Folder 235)
  - Tupper, Martin Farquhar to "Master Jordan", 1882 Nov 4 (Box 5, Folder 236)
  - Watts-Dunton, Theodore to an unidentified recipient, 1882 Apr 16 (Box 5, Folder 237)
  - Wolfe, Humbert. Translation of Edmond Rostand's "Cyrano de Bergerac" (Box 5, Folder 238-243)
  - Aldington, Richard. "Ezra Pound & T. S. Eliot: A Lecture," galley proof, corrected, [1954]
  - Lampton, William J. TLS to Mr. Crane, 1913 Mar 25 (Box 6, Folder 247)
  - Long, John Luther. ALS to [Richard Watson] Gilder, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 248)
  - Lunt, Alfred. ALS to HWL, 150 East End Avenue, New York (N.Y.), [1969 Feb 17] (Box 6, Folder 249)
  - Anderson, Maxwell, 1888-1959. ALS to Samuel Spewack, The Ritz-Carlton, Boston (Box 6, Folder 250)
  - Sterling, George, 1869-1926. ALS to Donald Clifford Gallup, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 251)
  - Johnston, Richard Malcolm, 1822-1898. ALS to R[ichard] W[atson] Gilder, 33 W. North Ave., 1891 Jul 29 (Box 6, Folder 252)
  - Wells, Carolyn, d. 1942. ALS to Edw[ard] F. Allen, Rahway, N.J., 1914 Nov 7 (Box 6, Folder 253)
  - Van Doren, Mark, 1894-1972. ALS to HWL, Falls Village, Conn., 1969 Oct 19 (Box 6, Folder 254)
  - Osborn, Robert Chesley, 1904-. ALS to HWL, Salisbury, Conn., [19]68 Sep 14 (Box 6, Folder 255)
  - Corelli, Marie, 1855-1924. ALS to Mr. Sims, 47 Longridge Road, Earl's Court, S.W., [18]95 Jan 9 (Box 6, Folder 256)
  - O'Hara, John, 1905-1970. 4 TLS to HWL, 55 East 86th Street, New York, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 257)
  - Mencken, H. L. (Henry Louis), 1880-1956. 4 TLS to HWL, 1524 Hollins St., Baltimore, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 258)
  - Nathan, George Jean, 1882-1958. ALS to HWL, 44 West 44th Street, New York, 1948 Jan 12 (Box 6, Folder 259)
  - Amory, Cleveland. 1 ALS and 2 TLS to HWL (Box 6, Folder 260)
  - Nabokov, Vladimir Vladimirovich, 1899-1977. TLS to HWL, Montreux-Palace Hotel, Montreux, Switzerland, 1969 May 30 (Box 6, Folder 261)
  - Lowell, James Russell, 1819-1891. ALS to Mrs. Boughton, 10, Lowndes Square, S.W., 1881 Jan 25 (Box 6, Folder 262)
  - Wilder, Thornton, 1897-1975. ALS to HWL, c/o Americ[an] Exp[ress] Co., 11 rue Scribe, Paris, [1957 Apr 15] (Box 6, Folder 263)
  - Wilder, Isabel, 1900-. 3 ALS and 1 TLS to HWL, 1977-79 (Box 6, Folder 264)
  - Wilder, Thornton, 1897-1975. 4 ALS to HWL (Box 6, Folder 265)
  - Aretino, Pietro, 1492-1556. 4 ALS (drafts) to unidentified recipients, Italy (Box 6, Folder 266)
  - Manuscript fragment, list of names in pencil, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 267)
    Removed from Liebert's copy of Shakespeare, William, The Plays (Dublin: Thomas Ewing, 1771) (2000 3114 6:2:2)
- Oversize, 1940 Oct 10
  - Carter, Frederick. "The Old Actor" (in Series III), 1940 Oct 10 (Box Bsd, folder 244)
  - Day, Nicholas. Portrait of Arthur Machen (in Series III), 1934 Mar 31 (Box Bsd, folder 245)
  - Aldington, Richard. "Ezra Pound & T. S. Eliot: A Lecture," galley proof, corrected (in Series I), [1954]s (Box Bsd, folder 246)